♪Eager to change the planet's orbit♪
حريصة على تغيير مدار الكوكب
♪Unexpectedly, you've become the planned orbit♪
♪ بشكل غير متوقع ، لقد أصبحت المدار المخطط
♪I can't avoid the end designated by you♪
♪ لا أستطيع تجنب النهاية التي حددتها لك ♪
♪Yet you're nowhere to be seen♪
♪ ومع ذلك لا يمكنك رؤيتك في أي مكان
♪I'm determined to look for your trace♪
♪ أنا مصمم على البحث عن أثرك ♪
♪At last, I turned into an unknown star♪
♪ أخيرًا تحولت إلى نجم غير معروف
♪Wandering silently on the edge of the Milky Way♪
♪ تتجول بصمت على حافة درب التبانة
♪Still, I can't see you♪
♪ ما زلت لا أستطيع رؤيتك
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪ كيف تتخلص من جاذبيتك ♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪ أنا مفتون ومختنق على حد سواء
♪The cycle is disturbed and the flight is out of control♪
الدورة مضطربة والرحلة خارجة عن السيطرة
♪Eager to crash on the earth with a shooting star♪
♪ حريصة على الاصطدام على الأرض مع شهاب
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
= قصة رومانسية يان تشي =
=Episode 10=
= الحلقة 10 =
Move the stuff over there.
انقل الأشياء هناك.
Clean up here.
نظف هنا.
And these.
و هؤلاء.
Boss,
رئيس،
you didn't sleep well last night, right?
لم تنم جيدا الليلة الماضية ، أليس كذلك؟
It's OK. Get back to your work.
كل شيء على مايرام.  عد إلى عملك.
OK.
نعم.
Miss Yan, how do you like your makeup?
آنسة يان ، كيف تحبين مكياجك؟
Yan Ning?
يان نينغ؟
- Yan Ning? - Yeah?
- يان نينغ؟ - أجل؟
She's talking to you.
إنها تتحدث إليك.
Check your makeup.
تحقق من مكياجك.
Oh.
أوه.
It's OK.
كل شيء على مايرام.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Nothing.
لا شيئ.
Do you cook a lot?
هل تطبخ كثيرا؟
Not much.
ليس كثيراً.
I usually cook instant noodles.
أنا عادة أطبخ المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Try this.
جرب هذا.
What's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
I want...
أريد...
Cut.
يقطع.
Makeup!
ميك أب!
Gu Han, listen carefully.
قو هان ، استمع بعناية.
I know everything.
انا أعرف كل شيء.
You and Yan Ning slipped away during the shooting.
تراجعت أنت ويان نينغ بعيدًا أثناء إطلاق النار.
What if you were photographed?
ماذا لو تم تصويرك؟
It's one thing to be on the show
إنه شيء واحد أن تكون في العرض
and it's another thing to date for real.
وهو شيء آخر حقيقي حتى الآن.
I'm warning you,
أنا أحذرك،
don't pressure me,
لا تضغط علي
or I can do anything.
أو يمكنني فعل أي شيء.
You can do anything?
يمكنك فعل أي شيء؟
Then make me a boneless chicken feet salad.
ثم اجعل لي سلطة أقدام دجاج مخلية.
You look like chicken feet.
تبدو مثل أقدام الدجاج.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
don't contact Yan Ning in private.
لا تتصل بيان نينغ على انفراد.
You're a very popular couple now.
أنت الآن ثنائي مشهور جدًا.
People are watching you.
الناس يراقبونك.
Right.
حق.
We're a popular couple.
نحن زوجان مشهوران.
What are you going to do?
ماالذي ستفعله؟
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
Gu Han is calling.
جو هان يتصل.
Hello, Gu Han.
مرحبا جو هان.
Hello, Yan Ning.
مرحبا يان نينغ.
Since we're a popular couple now,
بما أننا ثنائي مشهور الآن ،
shall we release a song together?
هل نطلق أغنية معا؟
Release a song together?
الافراج عن أغنية معا؟
Yes. What do you think?
نعم.  ماذا تعتقد؟
OK.
نعم.
OK, let's talk about it later.
حسنًا ، لنتحدث عنه لاحقًا.
Bye.
وداعا.
Aunt,
عمة،
bring me a box of duck's web.
أحضر لي علبة من شبكة البط.
Release a song?
الافراج عن أغنية؟
What song?
أي أغنية؟
He thinks when we're popular,
يعتقد أنه عندما نكون مشهورين ،
we may as well compose a song together.
يمكننا أيضًا تأليف أغنية معًا.
Oh.
أوه.
I think it's a good idea.
أظن أنها فكرة جيدة.
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
are you sure you want to be together with Gu Han?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد أن تكون مع جو هان؟
I think he's nice.
أعتقد أنه لطيف.
And there isn't
ولا يوجد
a more suitable man right now.
رجل أكثر ملاءمة الآن.
Suitable?
متكافئ؟
I don't think
لا اعتقد
you should date him because he's suitable.
يجب عليك مواعدته لأنه مناسب.
When you get close to him,
عندما تقترب منه ،
do you feel butterflies in your stomach?
هل تشعر بفراشات في معدتك؟
Does it matter?
هل يهم؟
Of course it does.
بالطبع هو كذلك.
If you feel it's like
إذا كنت تشعر أنه مثل
holding a tree when you hold him,
تحمل شجرة عندما تمسكه ،
how can you count it as love?
كيف تحسبه كحب؟
Don't you think so?
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
Boss, my leg has recovered.
بوس ، لقد تعافت ساقي.
It won't affect my work.
لن يؤثر ذلك على عملي.
When do we film my new MV?
متى نصور الفيديو كليب الجديد الخاص بي؟
I know you've been resting lately.
أعلم أنك كنت تستريح مؤخرًا.
But you should be patient
لكن يجب أن تتحلى بالصبر
with recuperating.
مع التعافي.
No.
رقم.
Boss, I'm recovered.
بوس ، لقد تعافيت.
I'm really recovered.
لقد تعافيت حقًا.
Look, I'm really recovered.
اسمع ، لقد تعافيت حقًا.
Don't play tough.
لا تلعب بقوة.
Come to me when you're fully recovered.
تعال إلي عندما تتعافى تمامًا.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Boss.
رئيس.
Ah!
آه!
Useless leg,
ساق عديمة الفائدة
when will you recover?
متى ستتعافى
Oh.
أوه.
Gu Han?
جو هان؟
Are you Tong Yuxin?
هل أنت تونغ يوكسين؟
The flowers are for me, right?
الزهور لي ، صحيح؟
Um, no.
أم لا.
They're for Yan Ning.
إنهم من أجل يان نينغ.
I hear that you're a toxic friend to Yan Ning.
سمعت أنك صديق سام ليان نينج.
You usually lash out at her in private.
عادة ما تنتقدها على انفراد.
You're colleagues.
أنتم زملاء.
You should respect her.
يجب أن تحترمها.
Though she is a senior to me,
على الرغم من أنها من كبار السن بالنسبة لي ،
she's also my rival.
إنها أيضًا منافستي.
I won't stop wrangling with her.
لن أتوقف عن الجدل معها.
Next year's Golden Song Award
جائزة الأغنية الذهبية للعام المقبل
must be mine.
يجب أن يكون لي.
Wait.
انتظر.
You wanna me stay?
هل تريدني أن أبقى؟
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
No.
رقم.
Give me back the flowers.
أعد لي الزهور.
Oh.
أوه.
No, I...
لا ، أنا ...
Ah!
آه!
No wonder you won the Golden Song Award.
لا عجب أنك فزت بجائزة الأغنية الذهبية.
- Here. - Hello.
- هنا.  - مرحبًا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Let's begin.
هيا نبدأ.
OK.
نعم.
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
I'm just a half baked idol.
أنا مجرد آيدول نصف مخبوز.
I can't compare with a virtuoso like you.
لا يمكنني المقارنة مع موهوب مثلك.
Use your index finger and middle finger.
استخدم إصبع السبابة والوسطى.
Gu Han plays aloof to me
يلعب جو هان بمعزل عندي
but smiles to Yan Ning like a fool.
لكنه يبتسم ليان نينغ مثل الأحمق.
There will be a good play.
ستكون هناك مسرحية جيدة.
You proceed.
عليك المضي قدما.
I'll leave for a while.
سأغادر لفترة.
Three, two, three.
ثلاثة ، اثنان ، ثلاثة.
One, three.
واحدة ثلاثة.
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
I still don't get the chords.
ما زلت لا أحصل على الحبال.
Would you teach me every day?
هل تعلمني كل يوم؟
OK.
نعم.
If you have any problems,
في حال واجهتك أي مشاكل،
I can teach you.
أستطيع تعليمك.
Shen Zhizhou?
شين تشيتشو؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Our popular couple is going to release a single.
سيصدر الزوجان المشهوران أغنية واحدة.
Why don't you inform the crew?
لماذا لا تخبر الطاقم؟
You're a director.
أنت مخرج.
Do you know about music?
هل تعرف عن الموسيقى؟
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Am I good enough to teach you?
هل أنا جيد بما يكفي لأعلمك؟
Yeah, but...
أجل ، لكن ...
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
Let's find you a place to practice.
لنجد لك مكانًا للتدريب.
Hey.
يا.
Mr. Shen,
السيد شين ،
we're going to compose a song.
سنقوم بتأليف أغنية.
Please don't interfere.
من فضلك لا تتدخل.
Get out.
اخرج.
♪The past is scattered all over the place♪
الماضي مبعثر في كل مكان
♪I remained where I was and waited for you♪
♪ بقيت حيث كنت وانتظرتك ♪
♪Doing my one-man show♪
♪ القيام ببرنامجي الفردي ♪
♪The deeper the scar, the more involved I am♪
♪ كلما كانت الندبة أعمق ، كنت أكثر انخراطًا
♪The more I try to forget, the more I miss you♪
♪ كلما حاولت أن أنسى ، اشتقت إليك أكثر
♪Losing you♪
خسارتك ♪
♪I sunk in there myself♪
♪ غرقت هناك بنفسي ♪
♪I crash on an isolated island♪
♪ تحطمت على جزيرة معزولة ♪
♪Covered in scars, I need the antidote, while the rain is pouring♪
مغطاة بالندوب ، أحتاج إلى الترياق ، بينما المطر ينهمر ♪
♪You don't care about the thing I treasure most♪
♪ أنت لا تهتم بالشيء الذي أعتز به أكثر
♪In an instant my heartbeat is frozen♪
♪ في لحظة تجمد دقات قلبي ♪
♪Broken pride♪
كبرياء مكسور
♪Once impulsive, then regretful, does it matter♪
بمجرد الاندفاع ، ثم الندم ، فهل يهم
♪You turn around, leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪ تستدير ، تاركة لي مكانًا أذهب إليه
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪ كن تلميذك واستجداء الحب ♪
♪Broken pride♪
كبرياء مكسور
♪Once impulsive, then regretful, does it matter♪
بمجرد الاندفاع ، ثم الندم ، فهل يهم
♪You turn around, leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪ تستدير ، تاركة لي مكانًا أذهب إليه
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪ كن تلميذك واستجداء الحب ♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
= قصة رومانسية يان تشي =
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(is exclusively owned by Tencent)
(مملوكة حصريًا لشركة Tencent)